[Music]
hello hello hello hello I am streaming
for the first time ever on hermitcraft
everybody and online at the moment we
have Cub fan and good times with scar
and I've got a bunch of stuff that I
really really want to do today
welcome welcome everybody it's good to
see well maybe not see oh I can see you
in the chat say hello I've got lots of
stuff that I want to do today now I've
actually already recorded an episode
today and I've edited it you see the
reason that I'm streaming is because I'm
actually going to Norway I don't know if
there's anyone from Norway in the chat
but I am going away Norway I'm going
skiing for a week and that means I
haven't had the time to do my normal
episode stuff so I have got one episode
ready and I basically didn't have
something for today I've only got
something for next week so that's why
we're streaming and I've got a big list
of stuff that I want to do so there's
gonna be maybe a little bit of spoilers
today for what I've just recorded but
for the most part it's going to be
grinding for the most part and here's my
to-do list I need to get seven alight
sure which means going to the end now
here's a funny thing about me on
hermitcraft
where was seven months eight months into
this now and I have not been to the end
once I have not been at all now that is
pretty terrible i think i might i may
even get the achievement oh wait no I
totally have been to the end cuz I went
to go and see
Tango's head vault so that's a lie I
have been to the end but I've not been
to the end
hunting for anything so that is on the
to-do list to get seven light trip but
hopefully it's cows gonna join me later
and be my buddy cuz I'm thinking I
definitely need like the buddy system
okay like I can't go in for my my first
time alone okay so I need to get
terracotta and the main thing is as you
could see from the title my last diamond
I need to get more diamonds and it's a
bit of a spoiler why I've lost all of my
diamonds even though I've already talked
about it in the previous episode but
I've been making these
did you die boxes and it's got
everything that you could possibly want
the thing is it thank you for the super
chat by the way and it's just so
expensive to make so I officially have
one diamond and it's this one this
singular diamond so the first thing I
think we're gonna do is we're gonna name
this we are going to say the last
diamond and I think we should keep this
on us at all times I just think that
this is the goal we want to do it so I'm
thinking we collect a bit of quartz we
collect a bit of terracotta and we
collect a bit of diamonds as well so
yeah lots of grindy stuff for the first
hour of this stream and then we're going
to meet up with Eskow to go and get some
Elektra which you know I've been working
on these boxes pretty pretty much all
day yesterday and I've not got very far
so gonna need a lot of those like thank
you for all the donations by the way
they are most appreciated so in my base
I've got this constant problem of not
knowing where any of my stuff is because
it's all in this ness of a system it
really is like I have sand galore but
then I just start chucking rubbish in
everywhere as you can see the bucket of
milk here few arrows yeah so I think
what we should do is start off by going
that to gets actually no you let me know
right so here are the options we can go
mining we can go collect quartz or we
could go and get terracotta I'll be
listening or be having a look to see
what you guys say in the chat and you
guys can vote on what we'll do and we're
only gonna do enough collecting to get
what we need see I need the terracotta
for a project that I'm gonna try not to
show and I need I need the diamonds
because I'm dirt poor and I need the
quartz for that same project that I'm
not going to show you as well so I'll uh
I'll have a look what everyone everyone
thinks I don't really mind what I do
it's all got to be done at some point
probably a couple 15 minutes each maybe
something like that
I don't really mind if you guys just
give me a little second I will be with
you again enough in a bit I'm just gonna
change a little setting there there we
go okay cool so it looks like mining is
the big one I see diamonds galore in
there okay let's let's hop down into the
mine you see there's a bit of a problem
with the mining that I've got is that
I've done a bit too much of it and
actually I've got to go quite a long way
to get to get some diamonds now and I've
I've really yeah I've really taken as
much out the strip mine under my base is
pretty heavy at this point my goodness
when was the last time that I was here I
haven't been strip mining in a long time
I will be later okey dokey
so yeah I still got loads of junk here
this is the this is the bottle under the
the sea I don't know I've still got oh
you know what that is quite useful all
of that is quite useful
I might have to raid this I'm constantly
running out of dyes oh bit of terracotta
lots of stone and various other junk
look at this food actually we could take
some food man I was so much more
organised at the beginning of the series
when did I give up organizing everything
it was it was I was doing so well in
this is little bottle look at that
who remembers who remembers bikini
bottom
when is Patrick's house gonna be made
scar if you're watching are we gonna
make Patrick's house are we gonna leave
that to like the end of the series thank
you for all of the donations by the way
[Music]
right let's head down into the mine it's
all the way over here and we might have
to travel a while see like yeah all of
these are done so I don't know how far
I've got to run down to get to a new
strip mine
but we'll we'll roll try and acquire a
few diamonds and I think I think I want
to try and keep I'm gonna keep this
diamond forever if I if I can well I'll
put it on an item frame and we'll keep
it in the base and we'll remember where
we got to at the start of this so we're
sort of starting this new architect
project with mumbo but you know Oh hold
on now this isn't mine you know what I
should have brought some wood I didn't
bring any wood I didn't come prepared at
all
I've got junk look at this look at how
much TNT there is in here just tons and
tons of TNT and gunpowder please tell me
there's there's terracotta in here I
might not even need to go and get
terracotta I think I'm gonna have to
double back and get some wood though
otherwise we're gonna be mining in the
dark which is I've done that before and
I don't think it's a good idea so I
don't know if this is my strip mine or
because right at the beginning of the
series right the season X made the
skeleton farm and we dug a tunnel all
the way to get there this might be mine
or it might be his I'm not sure that's
why that's why I don't strip mine
anymore I don't even know where to go
all right let's head back I knew I was
forgetting something I should always
keep a stack of wood on me at all times
I think the problem is I'm actually
running low on wood I'm pretty much
running low on every single resource I
might meet like if I'm gonna buy stuff
from people in the future I think I'm
gonna have to use io u--'s I've I've
heard that that's the thing but yeah
I've also used an ie before and it came
back to bite me so I definitely want to
avoid that if I can is there some wood
in here that I can utilize oh well why
are there so many eggs in there other
words probably all the way back in my
base see like this is like the
underground tunnel that people barely
get to see because I don't I don't
normally show myself traveling through
here very much
no wood in here but terrico I am finding
lots of terracotta that was bare wood
not a lot okay let's see if we can get a
stack of wood and I've not done anything
with under here either I think I won't
let's take a look see now we have to go
through the
mountains of chests to try and find what
we're looking for let's get rid of this
terracotta because we're gonna need that
and again junk this is how I end up with
loads of junk I just ended up doing
exactly that bit with oh my goodness
this must be painful for people that
have proper organized systems I know
it's painful for me and it's my base
we're also looking for a bit cold will
probably find coal but that will
probably do for what we need we just
need a little bit so that we're not
mining in the dark okay yeah that that
should do I imagine I'm not gonna fret
oh yeah there we have spruce dogs
alright back to the mine has anyone seen
poultry man recently actually poultry
man might have made a small debut or no
ríos of re-emergence in my episode that
I recorded today oh my goodness right
let's
oh there's my cows so see this is
annoying because I'm there is really
nowhere I can go I could go this way but
the problem is I hit a ravine pretty
quickly I think I hit water and that's
that's never good it's just a pain to go
through there we go let's get some
torches in here and I'm appreciating all
of the super chats I could see a couple
of tens in there from Xavier GW silver
there's so many names I'm afraid that
you guys are gonna have to bear in mind
that yep see this is exactly what's not
about you know I could just plow on
through oh wait I've already done this
what the heck
see this is why I can't go shrimp mining
everywhere although that is the end of
it there so I'll just continue where I
was going
Tyler Matthews with 2499 thank you very
much my dude I really do appreciate it
but you have to you guys are gonna have
to remember that I've not streamed in I
think over a year so I am gonna be
rather rubbish at reading out all the
donations but just know that it is super
super appreciated I am real
last I don't know which way let's find
the water thinking like this is this is
exactly why I no longer strip mine
because I have no idea where I am
there's one oh man why did I do this why
didn't I strip mine in a normal way
where it's nice and organized I just
went and dug everywhere now is that the
way back okay let's let's commit down
here and see where this goes
no I think you guys now understand the
problem away well I wasn't too fond of
this skeleton oh that was the way to
zoom as base right that means that stop
stop stop stop stop okay so if that's
the skeleton farm no wait this is my
base oh my I'm back where I started
oh this is so painful okay right we now
know this way to commit and then as soon
as we find this free spot we're going
for it okay and this is why I went and
got the torches cuz zombats are
everywhere all right let's take let's
take a mosey on down here shall we oh
man and I think down there is a skeleton
farm so we can continue down here
although it might let's let's commit
here no let's commit here alright here
we go
and we're off hopefully we can get
ourselves a few diamonds to go with our
last diamond so I would want to know I
wanted to ask you guys instead of a Q&A
with me where you guys ask me questions
I'm gonna ask you guys some questions
and then I'm gonna try and I'm going to
try and see what you guys say in the
chat if like if I can do that okay so
I'm gonna ask you what is your favorite
moment on hermitcraft
for my series that's the first question
is there a particular moment
that stands out as your favorite moment
and you go back and watch it again see
this is brilliant feedback because then
I can do more of the things that you
guys love the most and oh my goodness
according to the statistics right next
to me there are 12,000 people watching
12,000 people is insane
that's more than a population of certain
countries that is more population than
my town probably that is absolutely
crazy future if I tried to oh oh wait no
that's just the skeleton farm we can
continue no problem but this is gonna
happen a lot we're gonna come into
contact with all the other strip mines I
see that's the problem with Optifine
with the dynamic shaders I just forget
to place them I'd really don't want to
create lots of spawn locations for one
if Scout hates it I've a career I
actually I messed up quite badly once
keV 468 said 17 pound 53 right let's see
so the pufferfish pranking Eskow poetry
man all the trailers oh the poetry man
trailers oh they are some of my they
were also my favorite things to do but
they took an entire day just to make by
themselves that is that is the problem
they take so long to make honestly but I
really did like them they're a bit of a
burst of fresh air
lapis I will not say no to a bit of a
lapis the chat is going a little bit
fast for me to be able to keep up with
some of the things I'm I'm catching the
odd word or two mumbo-jumbo you are afk
I wondered if that would come up that
was right at the beginning of the series
how crazy is that
so the mumbo afk song was just like a
joke that then turned into a machine
that this is a big coal or here it
turned into a machine which actually
ended up I I did what I said in the song
to be honest I said I was gonna take his
mustache I'm a man of my word I said I
was gonna take it and I took it
speaking of lighting up guys you need to
remind me to light up the caves as I go
along if I'm forgetting cuz yeah I'm not
very good not very good I'd like to go I
made such a fuss about bringing torches
and then just totally forgot because I
carry one in my off hand like I just
forget about it
and we've not come across a single
diamond let's just check yeah we're at
y11 that should be fine for diamonds
pickles on the seafloor it's actually
crazy that my little like jingles that I
would sing as I was going along they
have they turned into remixes and then
into memes it's absolutely in sane
alright yeah I thought it was gonna
happen soon we've hit another strip mine
as long as there's a bit Spacey either
side we should hit some diamonds soon I
think we might be destined not to find
another single diamond not a single
diamond extra ok so next on the Q&A
everybody write my next question for you
guys is who's your favorite hermit
except for me you can't see me all mumbo
let's so they say that I know that me
and mumbo share a huge fan base so
besides me or mumbo who is your favorite
hermit and who would you like to see
more collaborations with I will take
that into consideration man we are
really not doing so well on the diamond
front lots of lapis which I won't I went
I went to stick my nose up at oh man
we're already out so let's dump some of
this stuff get rid of day all right
we don't I've got so much cobble and
stone and that's not a good sound of
course it was a salmon it was a salmon
oh look up there that's the the
architect male system maybe maybe I say
we continue until we find diamonds but I
think we're almost destined not to get
any I'm seeing a lot of his girls in the
track I'm seeing a lot of eczemas
haven't really done a lot with X
actually I need to do some more
collaborations with oh that's a shocker
box I want that there we go that's let's
just continue shall we with our bad luck
ok right so I think someone says what
will you be doing this live stream oh so
I guess a lot of people have tuned in
since we started o diamonds
diggy diggy diamonds oh wait do I want
to silk this or just fast exit I'm gonna
take these as diamond door and will
collect the ore for now - is there one
hiding behind here no not particularly
hi luck Oh even got a crew affinity on
him okay oh well they got a bit of luck
I forgotten what I was asking I was
asking about the who who you want to see
me collab with and I was gonna say oh
yeah exactly what we're doing on this
stream so lots people have tuned in
since we started this so basically we're
doing a bit of grinding I'm going away
for a week and now I've recorded an
episode but I didn't have time to make
an episode for today okay so that was
that was the problem so I've got to do a
lot of my chores and they see every
episode that I do it involves a lot of a
lot of chores in the background the
stuff that you don't see so this
livestream is almost an insight into
what I have to do in order to make what
I need for an episode so got to do all
this mining now normally I don't strip
mine to be honest with you I don't strip
mine that's something that I haven't had
to do in a long time mainly because
Jevon gave me three stacks of diamond
blocks
I haven't had to in a long time but I've
now invested all my diamonds so we've
got to go and do a lot of chores for
some of the upcoming projects that I
need to do we are really out of luck
here we've been streaming 20 minutes now
and not found found 4.2 diamond door
it's not not particularly great I'm
seeing a lot of super chats that is a
really really generous of everyone
whether you're super chatting or
donating through stream labs I really
really appreciate it
but I'm not yet talented enough as a
streamer to keep reading out all of the
messages but I really really do
appreciate it it actually allows it
allows me to do what I do so I
appreciate it and even if you don't
donate even just watching is absolutely
fantastic honestly we are really out of
luck here we get with past mumbos
by now I guarantee we have passed it we
are way past it
nothing oh I forgot about the torches
yeah thank you yeah Thank You chair I
forgot about the torches oh I really
forgot about the torches
yeah mumbos not gonna be happy I'm sure
he's like he's probably lit up all of
his cave systems to have a really good
spawning and stuff and there I am with
with my dark caves hold on I'm just
gonna take a quick drink okay so yeah
everyone's I see a few a few donations
that say like is this is this a real
live stream yes it is it is a real life
ah I know where we are we've we have we
have hit X's skeleton farm which means
we may be past mumbos base at this point
and I think we're gonna have to just
continue I think we're gonna have to go
round this and continue because I'm
committed to finding some diamonds this
this stream just as long as I light it
up worship or no way this is a terrible
idea I don't know where the actual
spawner is but I'm hoping I can just
maybe dig around it maybe dig around it
oh boy yeah this is why strip mining is
not so fun especially this late yeah all
great here it is yeah guys I found it uh
we might have to double back this is I
didn't bring a bucket of water now
that's always an amateur mistake oh that
is a real amateur mistake in Minecraft
don't bring a bucket of water that is
that's about as as noob as it gets no up
one more block over we're gonna have to
go up to the surface soon we are really
not lucky today lots of people are
excited to see me live if if
live-streaming is something that I could
do regularly and it's and I find it more
enjoyable the problem the thing the
reason I didn't stream is or don't
stream very often is because I simply
don't enjoy it as much as making videos
live content is different it's like a
plumber an electrician
they're like both tradesmen but they
different things so it doesn't
necessarily cause you can make videos
doesn't necessarily mean that you can
stream I mean for example I am missing
all of these donations and I'm so sorry
I really made me to appreciate it was
the chats who is the chat saying cool
mumbo oh my goodness so I was watching
mumbo jumbo stream and there was lots of
memes that came out of it so I'm
expecting to see all of the memes from
mumbos chat the the boring bye was
probably my favorite because I know what
mumbo means that sort of stuff would cut
right through me as well absolutely
hello but so yeah I mean now expecting
lots of boring bye but please please
don't leave where we're on the hunt for
diamonds guys we need to get this OH
serious this is seed nut now I know
where we are now we have now hit mumbo
Jumbo's strip-mine this is why we don't
strip-mine guys so as soon as we hit a
few diamonds I think we're gonna have to
surface because we've been doing this
for 20 minutes now well probably like 10
but you know when you when you're so
unfruitful like this we need we need
that we need a heavy donation from I
Jeff in or con Corp or something they
need to buy a few of my own digi die
boxes and then I'll be set for a while
then I can afford some I can afford to
eat in Minecraft again
oh man with I can't believe how unlucky
we're a bit getting on this it's
unbelievable of torches thank you chat
thank you chat thank you I forgot again
you guys are better at this than I am
that's for sure oh man I really forgot
okay let's let's head back shall we man
how many blocks do you reckon we've
we've dug
I know roughly my coordinates we've done
about probably 200 blocks worth and not
got a single one I mean statistically I
think we've really been unlucky I think
200 blocks we should have come across
multiple diamond veins by now absolutely
let's craft up some more torches because
this is um this is what I mean about the
just the inventory I wish the Minecraft
inventory was bigger that is my that is
one of my major gripes so
over the years this has stayed the same
pretty much they added this bit but that
doesn't really help you except one slot
so since the whole game was conceived
the entire inventory has only grown by
one tiny slot and that's really not a
lot what I would like to see is a whole
nother layer or you know one here and
then one along the bottom think about
how many different kinds of blocks and
items have been added so that's a
jump-scare oh boy that's I think that's
a really good reason to have a bucket of
love water sorry that was a jump scare
oh my heart's going but yeah was I
saying oh goodness sake this skeleton
not only did he put an arrow in my face
he he put an hour in my train of thought
and now that's gone as well oh dear
maybe you guys guys can remind me what I
was saying oh yeah so the Minecraft has
added so many blocks so many items and
yet and yet we just we don't have the
space for all of those items we don't
have the space here or here like look at
all this junk look at it and I've never
understood personally this is just a
personal gripe now when we when
minecraft was started thank you for the
torches reminder everybody's like why
are we stuck on 64 now that was just the
way the game was made but what's the
reason for not making it 99 because then
it's still two digits but then you can
hold more and you know for hardcore
minecraft players later it sounds really
weird to call myself a hardcore
minecraft player but I do I play
everyday for hours on end so I must come
under that category now but for us like
you know your inventory gets full up
within seconds
absolutely seconds absolutely ridiculous
so yeah that kind of kind of sucks the I
remember in the torches guys I'm
remembering the torches I'm seeing lots
of bananas in the chat now that was
funny
cuz you saw it you saw the conversation
we had with mumbo I said you only need
to say it once he's like just once yeah
mumbo once you only need to say it once
bananas yeah once what does he do in
chat he spams bananas like ten times and
it was so obvious let's put some of the
useful stuff in here yeah let's just
dump some stuff in here and then we'll
move on we're really really unlucky hold
on I this is this is getting out of hand
because we've now probably done wore 300
blocks and not a single diamond from
normal mining we only found one in that
little pocket of water well thank you
for all of these donations coming in by
the way in various currencies that I
don't I don't recognize actually I I see
Swedish crowns I see I see debt I think
I must be Danish crowns as well oh not
boring hi
thank you very much Chris Chu it's very
kind of you you missed a couple I missed
a couple of all I did I miss diamonds no
don't mess with me I definitely didn't
miss diamonds I would have I've been
paying attention that's the whole reason
I'm down here I would not have missed it
please Oh for you you guys that worried
about my rocket supply look I've got
plenty of rockets that look this will
last me like at least half an hour at
least half an hour let's go I can't
believe how unlucky we are this is
absolutely ridiculous
Oh speak of the diamonds one diamond
really not a single this is out of this
I don't think I've ever had such bad
luck when it comes to mining diamonds
this is unbelievable sweet there's lots
of Ghoulies yep oh I may not have to
fight anything at this rate I probably
shouldn't fight this close to lava so
let's
let's check in here shall we let's check
down here see if what we got oh yeah yep
another one another one
lots of Ghoulies we should continue with
the QA so I found that really
interesting but I need to actually need
a quote come up to come up with another
question for you guys I've asked all the
basics you know what's your favorite
that's that's the thing where lots of
people when I go to like events and
stuff they always ask me like what's
your favorite mob in Minecraft and I've
always got the answer so I should really
come up with better questions than
what's what's your favorite hermitcraft
except me I should definitely should
okay but let's continue so later on I'm
hoping to grab lots of elektra for my
did you die boxes because that's where
I've invested all my money it's a little
my own my diamonds that's where it's all
gone I can't believe this are you guys
do you guys agree with me we definitely
should have come across more diamonds by
now
absolutely must have like three three
diamond or this whole time this is
ridiculous ridiculous I mean I know you
can do this thing where you sort of turn
you turn and that maximizes your
efficiency but honestly it's more fun
just to go in a straight line to see how
far you can get but yeah look look at
this just nothing nothing bad luck by
the looks of things ahead look I'm still
seeing constant donations flooding in so
I want to a lot of people saying thank
you for the thank you for the content
which you know I really love YouTube and
you know what a lot of people ask me
about you know why did you start YouTube
and truth is I didn't really like plan
to you know in a sense like I joined a
team called crafted movie and as a guy
called salted and he's a real bro he's a
real friend he's been there like I've
got a lot I've got a lot to say facade
he's a really good guy and he took me in
his team
and then after that we made wing craft
which I'm actually hoping to do a video
on very soon for my second channel like
a little let's play run-through for
people that haven't seen it yet and yeah
I'm hoping and then after win craft I
basically just thought I'd upload a few
because I cuz when Quinn crafts is this
giant MMORPG in Minecraft so think like
runescape world Warcraft that kind of
thing now I learned a lot about building
and I would I've arguably gotten worse
since then but I learned a lot and I
thought I'd just upload a few of my
techniques that I figured thy invented
when building that map and yeah they did
well and I enjoyed youtube so I kind of
I kind of fell into it and yeah I've
been doing ever since and for some
reason somehow I now have nearly three
million subscribers which is absolutely
mind-boggling to me but you know what's
more mind-boggling the fact that there
are 17,000 people watching there was
15,000 and all we're doing a strip
mining what is that there's got to be
there's got to be something else that's
more entertaining than me
strip mining I think we're gonna have to
give up on this soon my my dudes because
we're now half an hour in and we found
three diamond doors this is the biggest
failure I think ever and this is why we
should vow never ever to go strip mining
again this one the last diamond maybe
this is a curse maybe this is that this
is a curse on us oh my goodness so you
guys vote when we go up okay I'll I'll
pay attention if only a few people are
saying go up or if we if we really
should commit to getting the diamonds
let's press on otherwise let's let's
surface I'm not sure where we are
exactly
oh boy and I'm gonna have to have a
little glass of water because talking
for this long is painful oh yeah I said
seeing a lot of search for diamond near
red stone or now is that oh I forgot
about the torches I forgot about the
torches you guys didn't remind me
actually to be fair I'm not really
looking to much some people are saying
go up I don't think it matter
like if there's diamond door behind here
then I'll I'll apologize but I don't
think it actually makes a difference I
think like that's just total chance I
don't know I don't know how maybe I'm
not good enough in Minecraft to know
exactly what to to do really unlucky oh
my goodness I'm seeing a lot of people
saying go up but you know if we go up
hang on
mumbo-jumbo is is afk now we can't prank
him now it's just that's rude we'd never
we'd never prank mumbo-jumbo when he's
afk
now don't worry well we won't do any
prank ajaan livestream that's a that's
video content right there
that is definitely video content right
there I currently we haven't found a
single diamond above from these three
like it still feels like it feels like
to me because this is like we had an ore
vein of two and an ore vein of one it
really honestly to me feels like I
haven't found a single diamond this is
absolutely awful I feel like I need to
at least find one diamond ore vein like
a proper one not one of these one on
their own business a proper chunky or
vein of diamonds and so far hold on we
have gone we've now gone five hundred
blocks I think maybe 400 500 blocks and
we still haven't found a chunky or a
diamond door vein absolutely ridiculous
let's keep going then I don't want to
keep the the f3 open forever but yeah so
okay okay new question for the QA for
the chat what would you oh look at that
being goaded by good times with Scott
wait its hold on guys I'm having a
revelation here this whole time that I
mean this I mean this this entire season
I'm not exaggerating this entire season
I thought it was good times with Scott
not good time with scar that insinuates
scar if we ever have a good time that's
it it's the one that's the one that you
get and that's it that you get one good
time with scar and then the rest of it
is a bad time well actually his his
his his his can account is called bad
time with scar that I found today but I
honestly thought it was good times with
scar now that would make that would make
so much more sense sky i I don't think I
don't think that we were ever allowed
I've had many good times with scar so
maybe now that I know that it's good
time with scar
I'm not allowed uh I understand it is
the curse of the last diamond let's do a
little experiment shall we let's put it
in the end of chest so we're no longer
carrying it with us the last diamonds
back in there if we get if we one who
can have one good time per game okay
right right so we got rid of the the
curse of the last diamond if we now come
across more diamonds then we know what's
we know the reasoning but I have a
feeling we're just cursed at the moment
cursed with bad fortune on the diamond
front I've got to admit yeah I did I
didn't forget oh yeah I kind of did
forget the torches but I went back for
them oh no stop trolling me guys I know
that I haven't missed a hundred diamonds
if I have then I quit heracross oh that
means there's probably water here no
just a random bit of magma okay cool
actually you know what I really could
use redstone so I'm not gonna ignore
redstone anymore redstone is actually
really useful for me so remind me if we
see redstone as well oh okay we are
really unlucky I feel like I have to
commit because you know we set out on a
mission to get more diamonds i buy any
and all redstone now I need I need
redstone I've been doing some redstone
projects I will have you know and I have
run out very quickly turns out redstone
it actually does get sucked up pretty
quickly when you're doing big projects
now I I still don't fully understand
redstone in this game and during Mambo
stream I did watch most of it I had it
in the background listening and he was
talking about something I found
particularly interesting he talked about
how how perfectly floored minecraft is
he said it's beautifully flawed that was
the way the
here he phrased it beautifully flawed
and stop telling me this diamonds I can
see that there's no diamonds and I I
have to agree it really is beautifully
flawed and redstone is flawed in such a
way that I don't understand it and I've
struggled to understand it since its
conception so I can make things work in
in minecraft redstone but I'm afraid I
don't understand why it works and that's
a bit of a problem when you're making a
machine because I know what I want to do
I want to make this piston go over there
and then extend back and do this but I
don't know how it does it and then when
mumbo comes over and helps me I then say
why does this work and he tries to
explain and it's just nonsense it's just
it you know he explains it's like oh
yeah minecraft adjuster does this thing
and I'm like so how are you meant to
learn this it's really difficult
we've hit more water I think we've hit
water
more times than we've hit diamonds I
think that is an actual fact we have hit
we have hit water more than we have hit
diamonds unbelievable we've only got
about 20 minutes until we need to meet
up with this girl to go Electra hunting
so we've got to find that diamond by now
now I don't think it was the it can't
have been the diamond that was cursing
us we're just
we've just got bad luck how many win
we're approaching 600 blocks worth of
mining this is absolutely insane and I'm
I'm fresh I think cupboards gar have
taken every single dime hello let's see
if oh no I've got a I've got full
inventory I thought I could poke him
into the lava but apparently not yeah I
think cub and scar have taken pretty
much every diamond on the server not
just not just mine from the from the war
I came in from here all right let's
continue down this way oh boy this is
yeah this is not good this is really not
good we're gonna have to wait after
surface soon because even even my iron
will is giving up we're gonna have to
we're gonna have to depart
I think cuz this is insane I can't
believe it all I shouldn't have done
that
actually yeah that's all I'm an idiot if
I use the silk pickaxe here then I could
install a redstone much easier but then
I just have to break it again hour later
which is kind of annoying as well
alright so let's continue the Q&A shall
we well I forgot about the torches I
think we're way past mumbos base now so
I don't think it matters too much about
the we must be way past it Oh someone
make a montage of all the weird noises I
make when I accidentally run into lava
yeah I think that is a sign I think
that's a sign that we leave so let's
let's head this way okay we're gonna
head this way for mm a hundred blocks if
we don't find a diamond we're leaving
and that is absolutely depressing
absolutely depressing absolutely right
now you know what this might actually be
our ticket out of here there's not a
single diamond around here in this this
ravine doesn't look like it this is
terrible luck terrible luck I can't
believe it I wonder if there's air up
here well that was a pretty quick way to
get out but what a shame
what a shame alright let's just head up
out of here oh my goodness right so we
have the choice now which is still
pretty much we still have one diamond
left please don't tell me I missed
diamonds because I can't my heart can't
take it please be nice I can't take it
if I've just done all that that and I
cuz I can't take you seriously I know
you guys were messing with me earlier
but now I'm really thinking that there
were diamonds down there right where are
we in the middle of nowhere in the
middle of the way I recognize that oh ok
so we went straight under mumbos base
and then we did a little small turn and
we ended up back here mumbo is actually
afk right here so we'll go and say hello
shall we just say hello to mumbo
hello mumbo your heads on backwards
we'll leave him because he's a of khang
for a reason
yeah what a pity so let's break open
these diamond doors shall we I bet we're
gonna get even with our fortune three
pickaxe we're probably gonna get just a
handful of diamonds a handful of
diamonds believable right let's go back
down into the base that was a failure
guys the first 40 minutes of a stream
absolutely terrible and this 19,000
people watching me fail to mine diamonds
I am embarrassed to say the least look
at that how pitiful right okay is that
two note four six seven we got seven
diamonds out of a 40-minute that is
possibly the worst mining expedition
that has ever been done in Minecraft
honestly that is appalling that is
absolutely terrible
right let's see if we got some cactus
green cuz I do remember somewhere I had
terracotta lots of it good and that
actually might cut out one of the things
that we needed to do today so let's yeah
let's take care of all this junk this is
why I have a storage problem because I
just put anything that isn't important
in random chests and then I need it
later let's put all of that in seven
diamonds seven diamonds I don't think
I've ever had such a poor haul in my
life oh dear right that's a crack home
with dying some terracotta because we're
gonna need this it's basically just a
collectathon today we for anyone that's
tuning in
somehow the thousands of people tuning
in we we are basically because I'm going
away skiing I I haven't had time to make
an episode so we're streaming but this
is a bit of an insight into some of the
chores that has to be done when you're
not recording so I thought I'd live
streaming this gives you a bit of an
insight into well I guess my life and
ten creation on the whole except I don't
talk complaining about how many diamonds
that I'm not getting hey hey when I'm
recording you'll be surprised how much
of a video right when you're recording
how much of it's just silent as you're
going okay right so that's a little bit
where'd that go that's their science
arakata is one of the things that I will
need and that's definitely not enough so
we will need to go and get some
we actually have 15 minutes before we're
due to meet up with s Cal and then yeah
we have 15 minutes to meet up with a
scout and we need to collect quartz
should we go and collect some quartz
everybody or shall we go and get some
terracotta I need a little bit of
terracotta but I do need a lot of quartz
her boy right let's get rid of some of
this junk again or why there's so many
eggs in there oh geez
dunno why is eggs in someone's left a
bunch of eggs in there has totally
unacceptable
alright let's empty this shoka box to be
honest a habit of mine is that I keep
dumping stuff in shulker boxes now that
is a really bad habit that is a really
really bad habit not gonna lie and by
the way towards the end of this stream I
want to know if you guys enjoyed it so I
could consider doing more live streams
maybe once a week because you know I
spend a day 2 days roughly 2 days if I'm
on a good streak or to two and a half to
three days on every single episode and
that includes you know recording editing
uploading thumbnail all the other stuff
no one cares about video making thing is
no one actually cares about the process
of video making they just want to see
the videos right we got a shock box I
just emptied one where did it go right
let's go you guys soon let's go get some
chords I actually quite liked going to
get courts because it's it's i think
it's therapeutic although i have i've
gone quite a long way out into the
nether to get quartz
all right here we go thank you for the
spring lift donated 9 pound 31 who says
you deserve this from your failed
expedition thank you so much do you know
what's awful you donated more pound
coins then I found diamonds after 40
minutes that is truly just I can't
believe it those of you that have played
Minecraft and done strip mining even
without all of the enchanted gear you
find more diamonds than that I can't
believe it now here's the thing about
quartz it's going to be everywhere oh my
goodness Mason Kelley has donated $100
through super chat with no message but
oh my goodness thank you so much Mason
that is unbelievable oh there we go some
quartz already that is absolutely
amazing I hope I haven't missed any
other donations quite as big as that
because that would be terrible if you
have donated that much and I did miss it
I am so so sorry you guys know that a
you know an R streamer that's not
something I've done you know i've
streamed i streamed evo once once and i
streamed hermitcraft none hi this is my
first ever hermit craft stream and I was
I was really nervous so I had a proper
sweat on before I was like poof I hope
it goes well
took a took a couple of hours to set up
and I had to actually set up here me out
I had to set up this stream almost like
I would set up a video as well so it
took a long time I almost want to go and
see what a cub and Skye are doing but
they're probably recording their
episodes at this time I've been wanting
to record with those guys for a while
but they're just you know the Khan Corp
we got we got we've got to do something
about them they've retired now they've
they've taken their diamonds and they've
retired oh that's it oh my goodness
someone has donated one thousand half
HUF now I am pretty good on my geography
now is that I might be wrong
is that Hungarian Florent is that what
it's called I might be wrong that might
be wrong but I think it's Hungarian
forint I wish I knew more about
currencies and stuff but I'm guessing
I'm guessing sir I'd love to know where
you guys are from achi yeah QA time
where are you guys from represent
represent with your flags I do like a
bit of flag identification so you know
drop it from the UK if you're from the
UK your European buddies absolutely love
my European neighbours if you've got
that I will recognise all of my European
neighbour flags if you're from the US
big old US please drop your your flag
let me know where you guys are from
because it's always interesting I can
I'll tell you what you tell me where you
guys are from and then I will tell you
where most of my viewers are from and
we'll see how they match up because it'd
be interesting to see who I mean I'm
guessing that my friends in Australia
and New Zealand all the way on the other
side of the world are the UK you know
our best friends over in Australia in
New Zealand they might be sleeping I'm
not sure what time it is I'm not that
good on time zones so I'm hoping that
I'm hoping that they're okay I see if I
see a lot of USA South is that South
African UK USA Oregon Australia oh there
are some people from Australia Croatia I
went to Croatia last year I've actually
been to Croatia several times it's a
wonderful country and I also love your
neighbor Slovenia if there's anyone from
Slovenia please speak up although it's a
quite a low population country so I I
wonder us Sweden Cyprus law
Germany Sweden all of our best friends
Misha Canada Canada and now Canada's
somewhere I really want to go I really
want to go to Canada haven't had the
opportunity yet but it's high on my list
now we are having such a good time
collecting this quartz because it's
everywhere
and that's what we want to see oh my
goodness
and yes someone said yes it's Hungarian
Florent so I was right I'll forint not
Florent oops my bad ok so I was I was
kind of right thank you for the donation
again that's very kind of you oh boy
alright we are approaching 10 minutes
countdown until we go into the end this
will be my first ever in Minecraft mind
ever this will be my first ever journey
into the end to go and raid it for
anything so that's why I've invited a
scout to join me on today's little
adventure because I think it's a wise
move to have the buddy system
I think the buddy system in the end is a
very wise move because if you do die
your stuff can be recovered by your
buddy and then it's not so devastating
if you do if both of you die then it's
it's catastrophe absolute catastrophe Oh
Netherlands and seeing lots of things
Mexico Slovenia now are you just saying
Slovenia because I said anyone from
severe Scotland I'll tell you well I've
never been to Scotland Scotland is
within my own country in the UK and I've
never been i apple of Scott Scott's and
I absolutely loved them big shout out to
my friend dang that's a long name or
Scott major he is so he's so cool I love
him I really need to go to Scotland I
was going to go in New Year because they
have a big celebration there but yeah I
mean I've been to Wales a few times
right she went to university in Wales
now why did that explode I went to
University in Wales so I've been to
Wales many many times but yes Scotland
is somewhere that I have not been
despite it being in my own country which
is a real shame because it's absolutely
a beautiful country full of beautiful
people I know I'm a big fan of
travelling by the way I think the top of
my list would be I think I think top of
my list at the moment is maybe Canada
maybe Canada
I want to go places I haven't been
before so that's that that's the thing I
want to go to Canada I'm going to Norway
for the first time tomorrow I'm flying
out tomorrow
and it's I think other other other
honorable mentions India the Philippines
I really want to see more of Asia I've
only ever been to Japan so that's a
that's a big thing
Oh someone donated five and New Zealand
Dollars so that is a very bats you on
the other side of the world what time is
it must be late or early I'm not sure
thank you so much for all of these
donations it really means a lot I can't
believe how many it's okay so yeah I
promised that I would tell you and where
people are from on viewership on my
channel so the big one as everyone would
probably guess is America thank you to
all of my American friends because you
make up over fifty percent of my entire
viewer base now you have got a big
population to be fair now after that
it's actually the UK big ups my homeland
so we got the UK and then we have
Australia Canada so all of the
english-speaking world as you might
expect okay so that's not really a
surprise but then we have the
Philippines they make up quite a big
percentage of my audience lots of people
from the Philippines actually watch my
videos now that's actually because the
Philippines used to be a u.s. territory
and they actually speak phenomenally
good English well for normal English I
do not sure grammar on that one but yeah
they they watch videos and then you've
got all of our European best friends
Germany Netherlands Sweden Norway all of
those guys predominantly because they
speak such good English and I'm super
jealous of anyone in a foreign country
like that you know that that can speak
another language I mean the fact that
everyone speaks English so perfectly and
I can barely say bong shots is is
absolutely ridiculous like we're
terrible in the UK for second languages
and that's probably one of my biggest
regrets I regret not learning an
instrument and I regret not learning a
second language oh no no no no no bad
bad bad bad bad
Oh jump scare jump scare
oh man that's why I should keep f3 on
whoo oh boy so yeah a big shout out
basically anyone that watches my videos
it's a real pleasure that you do you
watch yeah so yeah I'm a massive
traveler and Norway is my next
destination but I really want to see
more of India and Asia right let's move
on shall we
it might be time to me up with this gal
soon I'll see if he's if he's down for
that in a bit I have no idea how much
some of these these donors like the
foreign okay so I might know what
Hungarian forint is but I don't know how
much it is now I don't know if a
thousand is a lot but it's it's for some
reason on the super chase we've lasted a
long time so I'm guessing it's a big
amount
well maybe YouTube's been fooled like
you could donate a lot of Indian rupees
and it might be massive but it might
actually be one pound but I don't want
to I don't want to belittle anyone each
donation is absolutely brilliant I
absolutely love it Oh have I I think
I've just gotten full inventory of
another quart so let's ditch this and I
think we'll continue collecting a little
bit more just four more minutes until
we're due to meet up with this cow and
go to the end oh my goodness guys like
my my office is so hot right now my
office is so hot because okay I'll let
you in on a little secret
so um everybody knows this isn't this
isn't a secret really mumbo has
frequently said that he presses shift
with his thumb with his thumb now if
you've got a keyboard I'm gonna try it
right now I'm gonna try and press shift
with my thumb Oh Mike it hurts it it
hurts
it actually it actually hurts to do all
that stickykeys
I really need to disable sticky keys
that's the second time that that's
happened whoops but yeah that hurts so
mumbo does that for some reason for some
reason he presses shift wisdom my little
recording secret
my little recording secret is that I use
a blanket okay I have a recording
blanket and Oh someone's donated $50 $50
that's absolutely insane I can't see oh
there is Vincent Fisher thank you so
much that is as an insane donation I am
really really appreciative of it thank
you so much and I have a recording
blanket okay guys so basically if I took
this blanket off you would be able to
hear me clicking and typing a lot easier
so if I'm just playing normally you
might hear you might hear the odd tap
the tap tap tap tap tap I'm so I really
don't want to hear that in anybody's
video so in my videos I try to prevent
that from happening now sometimes in
videos you really want to hear that like
if someone's really spamming it you want
to be able to hear that that click for
for effect you know but so just walking
around you don't want to hear it so I
put a blanket over my hands and it
actually it dampens the sound so much
that you can barely hear it or at all if
you can I don't think you can really
hear it in my videos and to be honest
with you so it works it works but the
downside is my hands are so hot all the
time all the time all the time they are
sweaty really quite sweaty right now
because I've been streaming for an hour
you know normally when I'm recording if
I'm doing it like a silent segment you
know like I'm building something and
there's no commentary I take off the
blanket because I don't need it
so I get a little bit of a break but
because I'm streaming I keep it over my
fans the whole time so it's pretty it's
pretty heavy okay all right I'm just
checking some messages nothing
interesting let's see if Scout just said
that I'm doing a great job I really
appreciate that let's go but if if Scout
is watching we should go do that so I
might message him shall we meet up I'll
do that it's gonna take a while for us
to get back shall we and that's another
thing you might want to hear when you're
recording is you my only hear the typing
because it's a it's quite a nice effect
like if
if I'm typing on a sign you might want
to hear the clickety clack right how
much we didn't really get much normally
I will do this for three hours I think
my average quartz mining session is
three hours and I usually get a lot of
quartz from that normally enough to sell
in my shop but I think the prices in my
travel wagon are way too high at the
moment it's full of sand it's full of
sand and no one's bought any maybe
people don't need sand right now but I
might have to take it back and sell it
in schalke boxes because it's really not
selling maybe we will we'll keep it for
the project that we talked me in mumbo
talked about in our episode we have 19
thousand people watching 19,000 people
absolutely insane huh I think that was
the jingle for someone becoming a member
thank you very much oh yes a sponsor on
the channel thank you so much that's
very kind of you
sponsoring is a little different
actually it's like a subscription on
Twitch I'll be honest with you guys I'm
not a big I don't really watch streams
that often so I've watched a you know
some of my fellow hermit streams
occasionally you know to see see what
they're up to but on the whole I'm not a
massive stream watcher so I'm probably
yeah I'm probably not not I'm not used
to what people talk about on these kind
of things it's a very nerve-racking you
know because on a video you can cut out
anything anything that goes wrong you
can cut out not a big deal but and you
can keep the best bits in with a stream
nope that's it what you see is what you
get all right let's take a look gang
lots of highs it's a I'm from Brazil
hello hello Brazil we're in Norway I'm
going skiing in Norway and I won't tell
you exactly where because I I really
want this holiday to disconnect I can't
tell you how stressful YouTube really is
like everyone wants to be a youtuber
these days like lots of people in school
they say ah when I grab I want to be a
youtuber but
there's a lot of there's a lot of
hardships that people don't talk about
you often hear it or people talk about
mental health and stuff but the reality
is is not it's not that great so it's
important to take breaks and when when
you say breaks it's not just a break
away from your computer it's not a break
away from your country it's really a
break away from the internet which is
hard to do if you're just lounging
around a home because you sit on your
phone so my goal when I go away is to do
absolutely no internet no internet
whatsoever I want to really really truly
disconnect now that's easier said than
done because I am addicted like many
people to social media to the Internet
and my entire life revolves around the
internet so it's it's very difficult to
to to get out of it but I'm gonna do my
best I'm gonna do my absolute best how
are we doing not not great on this front
I feel like I haven't really got a lot
but we might have a shock a box full now
let's check now can you imagine yeah
right it's cuz you said are you ready I
was about to reply too much yeah I'm
ready let's go okay we got barely a
shock box but this is three four five
stacks of nether quartz now that is
probably more than enough that we need
all we gotta do now is find our way back
to the the hub and it is probably this
way doing some dangerous thing escalade
she had to save a scout from the nether
once he he went and died in a lava pool
like that one and I have to go in to dig
out an area and save him
fortunately it all went to plan and it
was it was great but I think it's this
way you come to learn the coordinates
yet that is a good sign that we will be
heading back so I think I can take that
off for now oh boy we are an hour into
the livestream everybody and it's time
to go end hunting which will be more fun
I imagine
because one will be with our good buddy
s cow and we will also be in a better
setting than mining in a strip mine
let's be honest
thanks for streaming oh you're very
welcome and it's just it's basic I'm
basically streaming because I haven't
had time to make an episode so I feel
like I'm cheating I feel like I'm really
cheating but this is like this is like a
non-canon episode if you like so I might
make the vaad available later or I might
not I don't know depends how people feel
about that kind of thing so I might
might I don't know I might leave it up I
might not either way this is a non
cannon episode so this isn't like
episode 51 this is just episode none
this is just a separate live stream okie
dokie so right if we're going into there
I've got empty shoka box for the things
let's make the problem worse by dumping
more stuff that we don't need and
probably that and what else I'm just
gonna take a quick swig of water cake
machine one donated says love your
channel you and mumbo are my favorite
Hermits oh thank you so much I hear that
quite a lot that me and mumbo share
quite a fanbase it's really unique to
have that not every youtuber it shares
such a big fan base so it's actually
crazy because you know because people
don't have that it means that me and
mumbo can interact and it hits both of
our audiences in a big way and that's
really cool to see people absolutely
love it when we interact and Scout I am
ready what do I need for end reading do
I need anything in particular I probably
don't need I think I should take some
precautions maybe I'll take my ender
chest but I won't take won't take that
Estero has become a sponsor thank you
very much that's a that's cool all right
I'll take my in the chest with me I
might need the sword might need I doubt
I'll need my
machine I might need my tried in an
almighty my sword so I think that's
everything
fireworks I've got galore so I'm not
worried about that
oh boy okay take more Rockets out on my
dude I have got a full choker box full
of well mostly full of rockets I bought
a lot of rockets over my time on hermit
craft
alright I'm gonna join a scout in the
discord so give me one second everybody
there we go
no I should be on push-to-talk hello
Isco hello Korean hello sorry I was
muted hi
i'il so you are also streaming correct I
am also streaming and I've been
preparing a little bit of things here
okay so you are and you can tell me what
do I need in particular I've got plenty
of fireworks Oh should I bring a spare
Electra Oh actually mm-hmm I didn't
actually think about that that's a good
idea that's a good idea
bring a spare lighter I will do the same
okie dokie let's put that in there
because I need to craft one up a little
bit quick though I'm scared that I'm
gonna die right guys so I thought you
don't have to worry I got your present
as well so the rest sounds good
just a bunch of rocket let's meet in the
shopping district shall we yes I'm just
making a lighter for myself real quick
making how are you making analyte ro you
craft them with no no don't don't no
don't talk nonsense yeah no no you go no
you can be edited in 13 to your craft
and wood leather dude no you don't
please you can't you owe me you're worse
than my chat I'm gonna do it right now
no you're not no you're not
I'm watching your stream and you know I
do not watching my stream yeah I am
I've got it muted in the background ha
ha
whatever I called your bluff I wasn't
really watching your stream well I think
by the way you're no longer the poorest
hermit I think it's me at the moment did
you find Cyril diamonds I found seven
after forty minutes seven diamonds I
noticed I noticed the floor though in
your mining my dude what you're not
using a beacon yeah is that I I'm
assuming that's because you don't have a
beacon right I don't have spare beacons
lying around that's for sure yeah now
you see as a hermit it's kind of a thing
you need to have or I guess I guess well
I don't really I don't really say
because he the beacon would have made me
mine faster but I still mind 700 blocks
out and got seven diamonds it doesn't
stop it as inefficient as it was I still
mind 700 diamonds and what diamond has
like was one 0.3 percent chance or
something like that was it 3 percent I
don't remember it so quite a low percent
but statistically speaking I should have
found about 10 times more diamonds than
I did okay whatever you say bro I'm just
saying real Hermits have a mining beacon
in the rent and real friends and real
friends supply each other with stuff
they need and so I said to you I've got
a gift for you for this end ring oh well
I might I'm waiting my my am my greens
laser
I mean travel I'm at the traffic cop oh
ok ok ok ok
I'll be with you in a second just in two
just need to pick something up he's not
here he's not here he was lying
he's not gonna give me a beacon is he
cuz I'm gonna have to I'm gonna have to
put that put that away I don't wanna
lose it I know the risks of the end guys
I know that there's a high chance you
can die I'm here in a second grip is he
gonna fly in like Superman should we do
should we do like a little tune are you
gonna told me dude where are you okay
never mind
he doesn't get a superhero-themed he's
I'm here okay so what we need for the
end raid we need a good sword you have a
good sword yes good we need a bowl you
have a good bowl that's a negative I've
not used a bow this whole season yeah
yeah yeah good luck with that you got a
good pick axe yeah you got deer worthy
of dying for I yes because you may lose
it you okay you got an in lighter yeah
you got a spare light shine your ender
chest and the most important thing of
course you brought a shield to block
those Alko shooter
no no luckily I thought about you and
made Yoshi you knew you knew that I
wouldn't have a shield pink shield pink
shield yes please this is just my
country this is just this pink shield
yes please this is just my color this is
just all this is brilliant I love this
do you have food as well by the way yes
I got plenty of food I'm good okay I'm
gonna give you this because I'm a real
friend and I want you to in the future
be able to mine like a real hermit so
you got a you got a beacon as a little
gift I'm just gonna I'm just gonna I'm
just gonna say things like real hairnets
don't build like that to you and see how
you feel well you are a real hermit
that's what I'm saying welcome to the
club I just gave you a freaking beacon
Wow
no that's good it's good that we met up
here because if you want to I tell if
you want to donate something in the
future to me like diamonds for example
then this is the chest to deuce you know
I have oh yeah okay I'll donate is there
gonna be do you have any idea how many
times I've emptied this thing of eggs
it's gone it's gone hear me sixty-four
diamonds in the hand it was gonna put
them in and then the chest is full of a
every time I pass this I fill this full
of eggs so no one no one could donate
any diamonds too because it's always
full of eggs I'm sorry my dude III it
wasn't even me how do you know as me are
you gonna blame the man and the chicken
costume well you know I wasn't but you
know like now that I mention it I wasn't
I wasn't gonna bring it up but like it
wasn't me it was the man in the chicken
costume try that okay that one that one
was me I only had four eggs because I
was I just had those in my adventure ii
by chance but like you know the guy
that's been just filling that up with
eggs dude not me I think I found it
rather hilarious that you've actually
prepared everything for the end yet your
inventory has four random eggs in it
yeah I find that rather weird dude weird
nah nah Cup fans donated I'm Yakko fan a
comfort has donated diamond diamonds at
least Korean see ya but a true bro gives
you life which is eggs diamonds aren't
alive
got a donation for a boy Jackson he says
go green you are the best thank you for
spelling my name right oh we are this is
the first time I've ever been to the
area
hmm I I went once to see tangos vault
and that's it where did you go I've lost
you laughter another P Noah never mind
yeah all right Leia nude
[Laughter]
here we are I think I have been him oh
yeah no I totally been here do you
remember when I flew through do you do
you know where we're going by the way no
no no I do
oh I should have brought pumpkin because
I have a bad habit of looking at a
Enderman yeah this is gonna go great
yeah this is this is why you need the
buddy system dude this is why you have
the end buddy system but I didn't bring
ender pearls that's fine just kill an
Enderman there we go all right let's go
you lead the way what hold on a to tell
someone I need to tell you I need to
tell you which direction we're going in
yes
all right we can go northeast southeast
and northwest south okay northeast
southeast Northwest
let's just go north okay so yeah
northeast sounds good
has this direction I'm ready yeah I
think we take mmm the cobblestone one
yeah the cobblestone one I have almost
looked at these guys like two times it's
gonna get a lot worse than this dude
this is easy easy mode right here what
do I do
so the under part in the thing yeah I
did it twice welcome to the outer end so
North East you said okay so let's just
fly let's take off [\h__\h] like that in
this direct I am so is the goal with his
end rain do you have a goal for seven
Elektra that's all I'm interested in
although I could fight a few shelters I
don't really mind I could go for a cup
of your Trident mmm-hmm what's wrong
with my Trident I mean it's gonna be
extremely tough but we'll see no shame
wouldn't seeing seven lighter so okay so
so if you want 70 light rest for
yourself so we need to find 14 then to
make it fair is that is that whatever
correctly but I might just here as like
a mailman buddy system party system one
way no way the one way bodies is this is
the one yes this is one way I think my
Trident is one way body system I try it
oh boy I hope my China's not lost maybe
we should let it catch up I don't think
you can lose it it's cow if he throw
your Trident into the end yes do you
lose it
did you cue it into the end my dude
maybe it just hasn't caught us
I actually don't know I've never tried
would never try that it sounds kind of
ridiculous to even try it
where are you I hope I already lost you
I stopped because I think I've thrown my
Trident into the abyss and oh my
goodness it's not coming back it's not
this is gonna be a good day in the chat
do you want me to do body system I
should fly into the void and check for
you I knew this is gonna go wrong I'm
still hoping that it's just gonna fly
back to me like it always has have you
got a spare or something yeah is that
gonna be a rip yep there we go dude the
only Trident I have is one that I found
and put mending on it has nothing else
but men have you got a spare bow I can't
believe that's so stupid it's not very
loyal is it the first chance it got its
guarded dude I've tried this tried to
escape so many times I don't have a I
have a fishing rod you could I mean I
can't believe it yeah it won't work
great I just I just need anything at
this point
I've thankfully I've been grinding
incredibly for for Trident sand I've got
lots pair but that was my Trident you
know that's that I've had that I've had
that first anyway yeah is my try that's
my fork I eat with that fork you eat
with that for exactly yeah yeah I
understand the feeling
why would you throw it in the void why
would you start by trying I tried what
were you aiming for you
see now I feel pretty good about you
losing your Trident because you were
actually trying to shoot it in my bomb I
knew I wasn't gonna hit you but I still
threw it I'm still hoping it's gonna
come back to me it's not good it's not
it has to hit something I'm sure it has
to hit something this is gone yeah it's
gone let's go
well I'm sure we'll find something good
I like you said you have extra Trident I
don't have any extra balls with me I
don't I I didn't foresee this and I've
learned the lesson I need to include a
new schalke box in my under chest called
the green box my next episode I have my
Trident in I have the Trident in my next
episode so that's the last time it's
ever going to get seen this is such a
terrible day donations so this is a bad
m-city if we want to look for it I trust
because this is just the tower
we need the bolts but this is unloaded
hey I got an achievement Oh what am i
doing oh okay I'm good I want to kill my
first shulkie go ahead
go ahead you want to use the shield to
block their things now that was easy
yeah this is a super easy Tower okay how
do you oka boxes is that all you need
yeah not chest two two things and a
chest
all right let's say how do you did you
use that did you just ask how do you
craft this all cool dudes I told you
never been in the end like I've just
been buying my shell cut boxes since the
start of this season that's hilarious
I think I know the direction you went in
I went towards the east
someone said have you always turn around
often I hope I'm going northeast yeah
you get away from me go tell me when
you're going yeah I will sorry I'm just
you know a veteran at this I'm chilling
middle if I see your pretty face soon
with a pink yeah New York no continue
continue there you go good job we did it
gang lagging getting a lot of donations
today I am I really really appreciate it
so there's 18,000 people watching which
is absolutely insane be really
interesting to see how this does in
video form afterwards
I don't really know what it what
YouTube's going to do with it
okie-dokie
we're not getting much luck here
I think I've lost him I looked away for
to set up there is not much luck this is
terrible dude is absolutely terrible so
far but I remember doing this with
mumble last time I remember flying out
to like 8,000 but before we found we hit
the wall with the world border before we
hominid and just make sure your lighter
is doing okay dude yeah well here we go
here we go
yay to the boat to the vault
are you in the vault
yeah I'm just where's the elektra
letting you take with you number one
there it is I already looted the chest
see now you can have whatever's in the
chest let me put this in the ender chest
so we don't lose it
good and I'll just put pick up the
schalke shells that you they didn't pick
up now if we want to we can also loot
some of these houses are actually really
good generally speaking it's the bigger
square cube boxes that we want to go for
wait what are we doing we ready oh I
need Weathers what we're doing we're
going to get more stuff yeah I mean we
may just well get a little bit like
there are some chests here with diamonds
and stuff in them dude you said you were
poor I can find diamonds looting the end
yeah so I'm over here you can see me and
you can go to your own thing
oh my all right guys I'm not sure what
I'm doing that sounds like something is
coming to get me what you know what
getting up getting up there's not as
easy as it looks you know what we'll
leave that for now I'm guessing you do
no damage when they're closed
oh no it's happened guys I thought I was
gonna get away with no no none of this
flying nonsense all these guys hurt wow
this was probably a bad idea I'm not
used to the techniques of fighting in
here I can get these guys yeah
stupid stupid stupid I should have
brought milk that's why I should have
brought right don't curse of binding of
course at queer affinity I'll take that
is it is it worth taking cursive binding
at all oh I don't even know I don't even
know are you okay my dude or are you
dead I'm just checking up on my buddy
I'm good good tear its curl anything
with cursive bindings not worth picking
up is it unless it's for a prank okay
I I've opened two chests or two sets of
two so four chests and in both of those
two sets of two I've got the exact same
items with the exact same enchants
I feel like there's a bug here if you
got the same as well because it has
curse a binding did you get did you get
boots and a hat yes
a queer affinity and I'm breaking free
yeah me too
oh my goodness did you just jump down
and get all my shellfish else that I've
fought for no I don't know where they
went
and I'm thinking ended and picked him up
in the overworld he blames the chicken
in the end he blames the Enderman how
convenient
how convenient oh for goodness sake this
I should have brought milk oh no you
just want to make sure you use your
shield milk isn't really worth it it's
kind of fun to be flying because milk
doesn't stack you see is it worth going
around here if all of the things are the
same no we can we can leave this place
now but we'll keep these items in mind
because I want to see if the whole end
is by now for us because that's
certainly not how it should know yeah
it's definitely broken it could have
been a good chest of these at least yeah
I mean this decent right yeah that's not
bad but that's not bad but I would have
liked some diamonds
okay I'm going northeast then where yeah
dude it's so hard to fly with the shield
you can take it off or we fly have you
flown away cuz I was waiting yeah I'm
flying I see I'm following okay okay I
got an enderchest that's pretty decent
yeah you get an enderchest per one of
those big rooms as well that's good but
it's gonna be into like think about it
think of all the lutes tables are broken
in every single one but they're
different per n cities so then we may
find one that has a little table of five
six diamonds and every find that yes I
wonder if it might be the whole end has
the same chest and then in which case
like how would be horror that would be
horrible but if it's just the end city
we could just get really lucky like if
there's like ten diamonds like easy
money yeah
amount of rockets crap oh look who's not
prepared now
oh I'm not out of rockets I'm just out
of rockets in my inventory I'll take it
back yeah I actually went to mumbles
base earlier today stole his gun powder
with permission stole his paper is it
stealing if it's with permission just a
question no I guess it's not
no luck over here I'm following you
right now keep going I'm gonna I'm gonna
blow my note gross he's gross guys well
he's blowing his nose let's have a
little read mega gibble donated five and
said rip the AK oh we've hit the book
we've hit the border if I hit the border
do I die he's blowing his nose no no but
this was unbelievably bad luck let's
continue what did he say
North by southeast right so he said
north east southeast and northwest so we
should go Northwest well we should just
head west really okay yeah so let's
continue north and then west because if
someone's gone straight west which is
usually what these people in between
will be done I should probably find you
though right yeah I'm by the wall flying
north I got the wall on my right hand
side oh boy yeah not gonna find you
probably I'm at 5900 by minus seven
thousand nine now
okay stay stay there okay 5000 watt and
eight hundred five thousand nine hundred
by minus eight thousand you're are
really far away from me alright
I'm chillin
bananas lights your check yet we got a
check we're all good we're all good
we're keeping an eye out for the end
cities at the moment a couple more
donations come through so what's up
everyone that's from the arcade dad says
love the channel man thank you very much
I've probably overshot him oh no we're
just yet there is all right so you dude
that's good I keep going now
what didn't you think of my graceful
spinning around in the air waiting for
you I didn't it dude you were just
Illinois you were just doing nothing
sorry bring flour goodbye thank you very
much sorry I'm not used to push to talk
business
you got the tail end of someone's
donation sorry that's all right Ryan
fin Ryan donated 10 my child is telling
me that you have 20,000 people watching
you yes 18,000 people watching
that's incredible I got 200 that's also
good that is also good that is good and
you're on Twitch so it's not quite the
same dude
zero luck I see that there's a hundred
euro donation but I don't see it on my
okay we've got a thousand again I'm
sorry I see man chat but I must have
been a while ago this is pretty bad I am
miss guys complaining I am so sorry he's
gonna die I think you're like two
Staters I'm well in they like true
saying I'm good and I am so sorry I
missed that your hundred euro donation
that is absolutely unacceptable of me
and I am so sorry
thank you so much I guess a little bit
maybe that is absolutely insane thank
you so much
I mean our view distances this is crazy
bad I'm so sorry this oh here we go here
we go follow follow me hey
you take the boat you take the boat but
so now you want those sweet delight
wrists and let's see the chests no
different different little table one of
the new tables here six diamond oh is it
gonna be six diamonds throughout I
really wish I had my Trident now guys
I'm so sorry that I what hit me come on
come at me got you
he still got me let's see what's in the
chests diamond boots
I'll take these gems they can be quite
useful oh let's see what happened for
diamonds I've already made more than
half of what I did for a mining and then
we've been unlucky with with with end
cities right I don't know it's my first
time okay fair enough
yeah yes you have
thank you for your five dollar donation
it's actually quite fun going through
the end right got the Electra okay do
you want to head out immediately that's
a really bad idea I don't know if
there's any more I'm gonna check one
more room here for chests that was that
was so bad that was so bad yeah I found
the Endor room chest hollow the ender
room chest let's let's just chill for a
bit
oh my goodness
oh that was really stupid of me I don't
know why I did Oh another four diamonds
yes not too bad so I found in this in
these two rooms that I opened I found
ten diamonds check this out dude ten
diamonds hmm thanks for rubbing it in
you're welcome
your pink shield is absolutely brilliant
on you you don't need to tell me that I
know I look fabulous
do you see did you see that I made the
red stripe also to match your shirt oh
yeah I studied it's noted good because
the pink is for your eyes and the red
stripe is for for your shirt okay let's
get out of here yeah just go ahead buy
stuff I'm rubbish you this it's okay
dude
it's okay oh I found another room with
the chest I'm gonna check I did get a
shocker head my my dudes one here there
we go I'm so the new tables are bugged
at the are paren city I just got another
four apartments in the same room what we
have to report that to someone who knows
anything about tech I think is
interesting it might just be with our
server though my server to some weird
things
oh no that's what I mean like someone in
the community like someone in her me
craft is what I'm saying like you and I
obviously or mumbled the three of us we
could never solve why it's like this is
what I'm saying
okay are we ready to take off yeah I'm
ready shall we fly straight north then
sure let's go I am going north
I'm really not used to push-to-talk by
the way it's making this really weird
for me
I hate this don't tell this girl but
this pink shields really annoying I know
I need it for the shockers but like it's
actually really annoying cuz I'm not
used to using it like I used to
I'm used to right-clicking my Rockets
I'm gonna have to restock on Rockets
soon as well okay we got another oh yeah
I'm all for the boat yeah the boat I'm
going for oh this doesn't have a good
room though Wow oh my goodness
diamond you get more diamonds 10 in each
chest 20 diamonds in these two chests I
found more diamonds than 40 minutes of
mining this is so unfair and then
imagine price every lighter ten diamonds
each as well right this is how you my
server oh and so big donation came
through 50 pounds from Stephan Paulson
oh wow this is absolutely awesome I
think that might be a proposition that
just happened in the chat I don't know
if that's serious or not that is crazy
he said that I see you watching a
favorite home it's beside me and I love
you like green loves mumbo will you
marry me that is absolutely insane I
don't know if that is a genuine thing or
not but I thought I'd read out just in
case it is let's get my shield back
right
is there any big rooms in there or not
is it worth going in there
yeah I'm looking around it doesn't look
like anything for me because I see you
as the boat but I do like the captain at
this point in time yeah and the captain
and I my loot is like finding these
chests yeah I'm the captain wow that was
that was very I said I said that just
because I keep getting hit by the show
cause he said that I was just floating
up
lots of donations coming through five
dollars ten from Samantha yeah so he
can't hear me when I read out the
donations by the way that's why he's
talking over which is why I find this
push-to-talk thing very strange very
very strange all right should we keep
going then my dude
yes in a second let me just no way dude
give me is okay yes north north north I
didn't find a single chest in this one
well you got some get you got some good
stuff I got a stack of shelter shells so
far yeah I got 40 for us not bad how
many do to make a shelter box - so the
44 you got obviously 34 was from the
room where I can pick them up no so
that's good that's good that's great no
that's not true that's as a lie yeah
this reminds me of the time that I am
transformed an N City in Minecraft like
I obviously transformed a lot of the
things in Minecraft like every temple
and all that kind of stuff
oh yeah you just talking news rain or
the book yeah so I transform the Lone
Eagle right and the N city was one of my
favorite ones it was the most
challenging because of the way that it
looks
yeah it's really ugly yeah you got to
look good I definitely went the wrong
way I've lost I don't know where is yeah
do you want to go to five thousand eight
hundred by 13 - 13 thousand three
hundred okay I went the wrong so I I
flew just north but then a little bit to
the right
I've left the boat for you cat wait say
that again five thousand three hundred
five thousand eight hundred by -
thirteen thirteen 313 you got it boss
absolutely insane there are still 18,000
people watching incredible everybody
absolutely incredible I'm really I'm
really really honored I really am
okay wonder where my phone is
oh there is I haven't seen it sorry I
know me check my phone at some point and
okay Mia right I'm here with you good
you can go to the bowl time left before
you dude but if they're there gotta be a
chest room in this place no no I forgot
my forgot this thing for goodness sake
it's such a unique thing this is such a
cool it's a cool little mob the shelter
actually really unique that's what I
want to see more of
if there's anyone at Mojang watching by
any chance cuz I know that sometimes
they they do didn't teach us Lee just he
just left let's see what we got Oh
rubbish
frost Walker yeah not too lucky on this
front I think that we got our Elektra
which is why we are here so let's be
smart about this where's the Elektra box
there it is says anyone in Mojang
watching because I know sometimes they
do and I would really like more unique
mobs like I don't really want to see
anymore zombies you know like the husks
and the what look what the drown the
Drowned are just underwater zombies oh
you know these shockers this is so
unique I want to see more of this in
Minecraft you know I want to see more of
this alright let's shift over a lot of
this junk as usual keep free up our
inventory and there okay I got leg ups
no ok we are good I have done the done
the thing we're good to go okay
I'm just picking up these two shells I
only found one chest here very
depressing place yeah I didn't get much
just the Ilario no diamonds just
straight North North Eames are you
working for us yep yep Oh
it is definitely dude this doesn't have
any lighter though but I'm gonna check
it out
I'm gonna check it out anyway check out
the big room
uh-oh this is a boring room that doesn't
have anything like the car but you play
north then in a second I'm flying like
stuck in midair you know how it is oh
yeah good way for this take the dragon
head
the dragon head grin uh I don't even see
the drive oh the dragon head there's a
dragon head on the top of the ship is
there is that true scowl
is there a dragon head on the boat sorry
what'd you say
is there a dragon skull yeah yeah there
is everyone is telling me to go and get
it so I'm gonna go and get it oh my
goodness
why would you want the head because then
I said they said no because they said so
they said so yeah but the Drake okay
whatever whatever I'm not gonna argue
with your viewers exactly and neither am
i just the babe
I don't want to lose this I'm not doing
this every time but we'll collect this
one shall we
there we go we've got I've got the
dragon head problem solved
good good now come back to the other one
and then we fly north this is ridiculous
all right let's put a high weight back
on and we're off all right going north
again there we go unbelievable
I'm north of the little garbage I see
you okay keep going north for the north
it's Cal architect Lowell is scale
architect mole he doesn't know this by
the way guys but I've got a really
really cool way to invite him to
architects like using that letter the
ark you know it's got architect long I
want to I want to do something massive
in his base to to deliver that letter to
lit to deliver that letter I can't
believe we found more diamonds here than
we did in the entire 40 minutes of
mining it's meant to be minecraft not
end raid until you get some diamonds
craft it's unbelievable yeah it's it's
probably a little bit laggy because we
are currently loading a lot of chunks a
lot of chunks oh dear
that's a good sign though if it's
loading chunks it's more likely to be an
end city of some kind
Shunta lease says hey gran I love
watching your videos thank you very much
and primer a wolf game said hey agree
and I love all your videos especially
your build tutorials never quit being
you thank you very very much that's very
kind of you I haven't done tutorials as
much simply because they really hurt the
channel like you know I my channel grew
on build tutorials but unfortunately
they have every time I upload one I just
lose lots and lots of subscribers and
they never get many views so this is not
going well now again dude yeah it's not
good so ever I've had to stop I stopped
doing it so much it's unfortunate really
but that's kinda why okay to briam I
have to ask you a question I'm missing
you and mumbo both sent me a DM on
discord the other day it was a very
weird DM it said it's Cal do not watch
my last video I got that from you and
then I got it from mumbo as well yeah
then in my in my comments and in my chat
I keep seeing the following sentence
here it comes it's Cal is Cal architech
lon yeah it makes no sense well of
course
wait are you behind are you behind this
sentence well no no no we told you not
to watch our episodes because it's
important not to watch our episodes just
unsubscribe I did I did a media week a
week we got it we got I got a 50 mail
emails which I do daily saying subscribe
to mumble and subscribe to green
well I mean so then I have to vague yeah
exactly
you gotta listen to the fans oh here we
go no this is a garbage one let's check
the top floor five minutes I don't think
I'm anywhere near you I've been flying
well I've already checked it now we've
got four alight Trece with three oh wait
I found the same one okay we're back
nothing
I'm flying north nope garbage
sorry where were we a nothing you know
we were talking about the window look at
the density big one oh we almost wow
that is a okay this is one of the
biggest one I've ever seen
oh no I need to get my shield before we
go oh no come on yes yes this has bugged
out diamond chests
no how many how many eight at least in
this in this room this isn't good fellas
I'm for protests oh my goodness I'm in
trouble boys maybe I should just eat
yeah this is gonna hurt how many
lighters are you up to anyway I got four
at the moment five would this city yeah
five we are doing really good oh my
goodness these chests diamond I've got
boots chest plate diamond helmet pickaxe
a trial full diamond set brilliant yeah
and with good enchants some no not many
still it's free anger yeah this I am
GERD an Enderman if I die tell my tell
my brother I love him I'm so scared I'm
very scared hopefully this girl hasn't
done this one I can tell I'm gonna die
before this is up you way I'm gonna die
look at this look at this I'm gonna have
to it's too too much stuff guys I'm
gonna have to put it in Ashoka let's try
this one
nope I'm gonna have to choke her up
properly that's let's go and get the
stuff the electric box alright we got
lots of goodies here be a light trap
let's not forget the alight trap this
has been good this is a good this good
box and we don't really want any purple
purple I don't think I'll ever use
purpose being honest with you guys
that's actually get rid of that ding in
the ear hello
that is Brian Mayer saying the reason
I'm watching hermit craft is because I'm
watching home across seas and my
favorite hermit I'll thank you so much
and that is PHP 500 now I I'm gonna be
guessing again what currency that is PHP
sounds like it might be some sort of I'm
gonna guess Philippines I'm just gonna
guess I have no idea let me know what
PHP is because I honestly I'm interested
I'm take those out we'll put that in
might as well put that in for
safekeeping
nothing too valuable here alright let's
go and get some shulkie shall we oh
nothing here maybe your scales already
done all this quite possibly he's taken
all the good stuff and I've just been
left with the dregs do they all they do
teleport I want to clear this big room
before we go agree I don't know about
how you're doing you're very quiet but
I'm assuming you're okay yeah I'm okay I
can't tell what rooms you've done
haven't now there are a lot of rooms
that I haven't done I've only done like
one of the big ones
I see it's Mambo and he is really scared
of dying to shelters so I've always had
the task to do these big rooms because
these are a little bit crazy
and yeah we got it we got it we got it
of course that's that's nice loot for
killing one shark isn't it
I killed I killed more than one you
killed want I counted I think get that
many there's only like four yeah all
right shall we leave this place if
you've done them all yeah I haven't done
all the small ones but if you've done
the big ones let's let's move yeah
where we go north we are is that a
question at this point in time
apparently you brought the schalke box
of quartz in your inventory people are
worried before you might I I know if I
put it away I've put it away real good
I need a pit stop for rocket
oh I light your check you guys forgot to
do Alijah check guys man my my hands are
real sweaty really sweaty oh boy this
this [\h__\h] this is why I don't have a
shield they just get in the way Amy M
has become a member thank you very much
that's very I need a pit stop dude I'm
stopping on this little island here this
island here there are many islands like
this one but this one here this one is
mine I thought I could land there but I
couldn't that's just there look at the
ground mm-hmm
for how many diamonds have you made so
far whoa instant curry nice things in
the amazon project i think that might be
a wink-wink the plan wink wink thank you
for dropping I believe that's Australian
dollars a hundred Australian dollars
that's very very kind of you and
hopefully the Amazon project will be
something that everyone gets super into
I'm really looking forward to it even if
I don't really know what's gonna happen
yet
have you already started flying north
again yeah eight years ago found one I
assumed that you forgot push-to-talk
because you didn't ask me Freitas I
found one for you leaving the ship to
you captain
alright mas 5 5800 by - 21,600 it's
basically just straight north
we should find it if we go this way was
again 25,000 what 20 - twenty one
thousand six hundred and then five
thousand seven hundred on the first one
there we go I found it the bolt is all
for you let's hope we get some diamonds
in here as well I can't believe the
amount of diamonds that we've got just
from this end ring how many diamonds
have you earned so far do you have any
idea about twenty four yeah this is the
way to do it I got 26 bad luck here bit
bad luck
oh that's a good pickaxe I think that's
number six we need one more just one
more and then we're done okay
let's get this stuff ready again man
this is a tough it's a tough thing I
mean streaming for me I'm already like
really tired I was tired when I started
streaming as well which doesn't help
let's put all those together put those
there
ah this has been so good look at all
this loot but I was really tired before
I sighed streaming and I'm even more
tired now
so I think after we've done this and
I've got my Electra the Electra was the
main task for today we did get a bunch
of emeralds not a huge amount I would
have liked emeralds diamonds I would
have liked more but it's a shame really
I would have liked like a few more
diamonds especially from that but it
turns out we've already got lots of the
Terra Cotta oh my goodness look at that
okay I'm done with the mega big room
if jumping out is there any other chest
room in this wall this place was also
quite big but I think that is it's four
chests I don't really know where the
chest rooms are in these things oh no
there's one here I think there's the
ones that have a staircase on the roof
yeah and then the big the big thing in
the middle of this one is a chest true
oh no that's not actually what hold on G
we still have 18,000 people watching
just you know off to the side whispers
in the air 18,000 people that's
absolutely insane okay let's leave let's
leave I'm getting confused there's too
many Enderman here
I really hate the shield my dudes I
can't stand it I hate I hate not being
able to take off like I always can I
love being able to just jump and fly
away like a beautiful butterfly
[Laughter]
someone has noticed that I have the
g-force r-tx 2080 if you look up in the
right-hand corner you can see some of my
specs and they're donated $5 saying how
is the how is the r-tx 2080
it is it's doing me justice I can I can
tell you that it is doing me justice it
really is I love I love this thing it's
I used to have to wait two hours to
render a video it's now like 20 minutes
which is insane really really cool it
lights your check someone they are debt
then donated five say electric we're all
good
Ben thank you very much for reminding me
it's always easy to forget when you're
engrossed in these kind of things you
know what we really we real quick do a
statistic tech my chap wants to know
something weird that I'm interesting in
how much playtime we have playtime all
right all right all right let me let me
pop myself I've landed where do I see
the statistics general be right down the
bottom I think don't at the bottom
I'm not a fk'd much I said time time
played nearly 30 days for me time played
time played I can't oh there yeah 28.1
days yeah so roughly the same and that's
I'm pretty proud of that I think I'm a
fk'd one night like I've been afk for
one six-hour session I I used to afk in
the Trident farm I think I fk'd maybe
twice in the Trident farm because I was
desperate to get one and you couldn't
get one at the beginning of the season
because there's too many people online
so it was real ah I got I got loads in
the end
so about 750 hours I just did some quick
math Korean Wow quick math yeah 750
hours that's that's a lot if you put it
into context we've been doing this
season for seven months
brilliant we've been doing this for
seven months so that's one seventh of
our entire time over the last over the
course of the season spent on the server
that's an insane amount of time for how
long we've been doing it and you know
what I'm kind of proud is that weird
no cuz now that's what we do I love this
game too much I'm getting rekt you're
gonna die are you all your on the bolt
where I'm just I'm just flying and
there's nothing I could do about exiting
on the bow oh I forgot about that it
wouldn't have worked without ride in
silence did no damage mighty heat I'm
sorry you lost your tribe I should have
left what was it called dear Trident was
it born it was born it was named after I
think it was Buren I think you said
Buren I think it's Cal I just want to
let you know that I've named your try it
my Trident after you know it was the
fork of friendship I believe oh no
that's Monday's no it was an aqua man's
big fork but I think I renamed a car
remember it was called this joker needs
to let's just let's just let's just
agree to disagree that we named it the
you namely purifies it definitely 100%
was not the name like 100% shaded it was
not it was not whatever he says it was
not named Bo and we all know it oh
there's another one it's not so bad in
here though I'm really bad at this game
right look time zero luck zero luck
cursive
what does Vanette curse of vanishing
mean so when you die using that item it
will actually be destroyed as if a Udine
lava so it can be good if it's like a
good item I mean I don't mind it on a
pickaxe that I find you know I've got
I've got enough I'll leave it right you
done here yeah sure
we're done we're done with the whole
thing we're done we got all seven
oh my dudes we
finished okay let's land safely over
here leave the rest of this yeah we have
to get back gotta get some man yeah I'll
fix tough words I've already covered
that
you think I'm brand new come to me I
flew down west of this thing at five
five five five minus twenty five
thousand two hundred in the course
frequency sorry said again
I flew I'm sitting at 5555 by minus
twenty five thousand two hundred it's
it's just directly west of there okay
yeah I see you I see you I'm gonna catch
you all right okay I got it I'm gonna
give you an ender pearl there you go
okay okay and now we're gonna fly to
five thousand eight hundred which is
just three hundred bucks by -22 I'm just
gonna follow him thousand nine hundred
so that is south yeah South by a little
bit east not much apparently much full
of me even have a name okay
a scow architect law is now a thing
screen says Jack Jack Jack is I mean
it's Jacques Jacques no yeah maybe over
bed don't need to turn saying thanks for
the entertainment miss season and
increasingly to all the hermit's you're
the best thank you so much that really
does mean a lot it's actually crazy how
this thing old ah dude I'm gonna need to
restock on rockets I'm out I'm landing
panic that he's a noob he says he's an
expert this game he's a noob
I've got to say guys we're heading
towards the end of the stream I think
when we get back to the base that will
we're over two hours that's I think
that's about as much as I can normally
know you're with me sir yeah I'm with
you bro I'm with you bro and but I want
to say a big thing was there I really do
wanna say I want to say huge huge huge
huge thank you to absolutely everyone
that's donated big and small little and
big everything because it really does it
means that this is made up this live
stream has really made up big time more
than ever then you know uploading a
video and yeah I've quite enjoyed this
I've had something to do not not it's
not normal that I have okay something
like this I don't normally have like
these big grinding things I have neither
up to this thing so yeah I want to say
big thank you to everyone because this
has been a real experience and maybe I
should live stream more and I did say
this earlier but I'd love to hear what
you guys have thought and if you want to
see more of these then please please
PLEASE nicely thank you and you know
what to do OOP are you through
oh now how do we get back oh we have to
go in the dragon portal now man this
place is a mess you know what maybe next
season we should do like because there's
a I think there's like these pillars
they go all the all the way through you
should I should split our loot err I
guess so oh I'm back at spawn island oh
no I'm back in my bed yeah well that's a
successful end raid are you happy yeah
very good B yeah very very happy thank
you for being my buddy on that wouldn't
been able to do it other way the one way
body we don't we died without 0 times
yeah we did that's pretty pretty awesome
this is what mumble did his first six
times
okay oh man that is a good good amount
of Lu I'm gonna use those I'm gonna use
all this armor I'm gonna use all these
pickaxes I'm gonna put the Shocker box
in my head
collection which is right here I've got
quite a lot of them I need to get more
actually and where did it go
wait which one was it there's problem 30
diamonds how how bad is that case
seriously we got seven diamonds seven
diamonds that entire mining session and
we got thirty doing the end raids we
should have just n raided for double the
amount of time and we would have had
more thirty-seven diamonds for a
two-hour session is terrible you can
normally get more diamonds than this
like a stack of diamonds in an hour you
know just from mining we just had such
bad bad luck I realize that I've been
saying that there's 18,000 people in the
chat but it hasn't fluctuated that the
the thing that it says there on the
right 18,000 it hasn't changed so I'm a
little bit suspicious I don't know how
many people are actually watching which
is so I read out a few more donations
before we say goodbye but I want to ask
you guys QA question did you enjoy the
stream would you like to see some more I
could do this once every fortnight once
a month I might even join in on the
hermit craft stream days I don't know
this has been a good experience actually
I want to get better at it
I actually personally think I've done
better than I thought I would
considering how nervous I was someone
said wasted two hours of my day thanks
Korean no worries I've not wasted my two
hours okay so Cod donated one pound
seventy one he says greetings from
Prague in the Czech Republic absolutely
love the Czech Republic and we have
Gawain who donated says Samsung is
better than Apple
okay whatever floats your boat fin says
thank you for the lovely video
grim what was your loot in the end like
how many soldiers did you get how many
diamonds did again I know you took all
their lighters and I'm fine with that
you can have I got a stack of shelcha
shells I got a good amount I've got like
four diamond horse armor and seven
letters if you want any of it just pop
over I'll give you how many shark shows
did you get no I don't want them you
keep it I got two stacks of schalke
shells plus ten and twenty six diamonds
and then lots of half good armor tool
okay I got a I actually got thirty
diamonds so I'll write you an IOU no you
know what you know what I'm so proud of
being your buddy in this fight I'm so
proud of your performance that I think
you should keep them because you are a
poor man than me right now and for me
it's valuable to be for the first time
ever saying that I'm not the poorest
tournament and I appreciate that but
anyway I'm sure I'm sure things will
work out in the end anyway this is where
I'm going to say goodbye Scout thank you
for joining me
I'm sure everyone has enjoyed your
presence here and helping us out it
would have been a lot more painful
watching me do that alone I wouldn't
even know where to go so thank you
alright so thank you very much as I was
saying to everyone that has donated and
all that good stuff like it's it's been
absolutely amazing I've seen I'm seeing
a lot of people saying there was a good
livestream they they enjoyed it I'm
seeing a lot of it scale architect Lal I
think I might actually link s Kyle's
twitch I don't know if he's going to be
streaming any longer but we could send
some people over there wow this has been
absolutely brilliant I'm just gonna read
through some of the last Super chats and
then we will go and say good night cuz
it is it is it's getting late for me
alright so the doctor says donated $50
$50 but goodness gracious me I vote to
do more live streams I love this well I
am very very thankful thank you very
very thankful indeed I'm so glad that
you enjoyed the live stream we have Alex
Louie who's donated some New Zealand
Dollars thank you very much
Minnie boy donated five
says you should play for tonight again
they let you build whatever you want
with no enemies I actually tried that
out on fortnight and I just I just
didn't get on with the system I need a
inventory you know like like minecraft I
need I need this I need this I need this
to work
Philip says started watching hermit
craft when you join been tons of laughed
enjoy your disconnect time spend time in
nature I will definitely try to do that
spark says thank you so much for
introducing me to hermit craft and
mumbos channel and I now have Murchie
for you both oh that's absolutely
wonderful thank you so much big it's
absolutely incredible I really really
appreciate it it's weird to me that I've
introduced people to mumbo I would have
thought mostly it would have been you
know mama has been doing this a lot
longer than me been established longer
than me so I thought it you know it does
go both ways I guess I should remember
that every now and again second nature
pigs had donated eight pounds saying
boring by not boring by glitch donates
in a raid G team base for diamonds there
was never any diamonds there never any
diamonds there we didn't have diamonds
to spare around there okay alright thank
you very much for watching everybody
this has been absolutely amazing and I
want to say a big thank you again and
good